(Raj:)I don't appreciate
your sarcasm,
(Raj:)but we've still got two blocks
to go, so I'll put up with it.
(Amy:)Whatever happened with
your online dating?
(Raj:)No one was writing me back,
so I stopped checking my profile.
(Amy:)Before I met Sheldon,
I was ready to give up, too.
(Amy:)Once, I even dropped
in on my OB/GYN
(Amy:)just to get some
human contact.
(Raj:)It has been a while
since I got my prostate checked.
(Amy:)Then I met Sheldon
and look at where we are now.
(Raj:)What? You've kissed, like,
once in three years.
(Amy:)That's true.
Do whatever you want.
(Howard:)-Hey.
-Hello.
(Howard:)Listen,
I was thinking you and I
(Howard:)could probably try
to be better friends.
(Amy:)Really?
(Howard:)I was thinking
what we have now is a bit much.
(Howard:)Seriously, I was talking
to Bernadette last night and